[rock guitar riff playing]
‎“远景巡洋舰”刚到你手上20分钟
‎你们就被警察拦停了哇？
Pulled over by the cops 20 minutes after
we gave you the Vista Cruiser?
‎谁会有这种本事？
Who could have pulled off
something like that?
‎肯定是犯罪天才 天生蠢材
Only a criminal mastermind
without the mind.
‎凯尔索
A Kelso.
‎摊上他们总没好事 亲爱的
Trouble just follows them, honey.
‎这种人就像雨林里的青蛙
They're like those frogs
in the rainforest.
‎颜色艳丽
Colorful and pretty,
‎可舔一下就得掉皮送命
but if you lick them,
all your skin falls off and you die.
‎不好意思 能不能先别说了？
I'm sorry, but can we just stop
for a second?
‎我们在牵手唉 这是有多萌？
Because how cute is this
that we are holding hands? [chuckles]
‎同志们 我俩终于在一起了
It finally happened, you guys!
‎爷爷 我知道后果似乎很严重
‎但我们之所以被拦停
Grandpa, I know this looks bad,
but we only got pulled over
‎是因为车牌还是1980年的
because the car had
license plates from 1980.
‎她说的对 福尔曼先生
She's right, Mr. Forman.
‎有时 怨人不如问己
Sometimes, if you're searching for blame,
it's best to look inward.
‎那我就自己踢你屁股
My foot's about to go inward your ass.
‎你纯粹是自找没趣
You can't set him up like that.
‎我知道这个头开得不好
‎但请给我一次机会
I know we're off to a rough start,
but give me a chance.
‎总有一天 这只青蛙会变成蝴蝶
Someday, this frog
is gonna turn into a butterfly.
‎我站在这儿 智商噌噌往下掉
I'm getting stupider standing here.
‎以后不许你来这个家 出去
You are banned from this house. Get out.
‎什么？不行！
What? No!
‎亲爱的 放开那只青蛙
Honey. Honey.
Let go of the frog.
‎一 二 三 四
-[rock music playing]
-One, two, three, four!
‎在街上闲逛
♪ Hangin' out down the street ♪
‎和上周没什么两样
♪ The same old thing we did last week ♪
‎没什么事好做 就跟你唠唠嗑
♪ Not a thing to do ♪
♪ But talk to you ♪
‎这样挺好 这样挺好
♪ We're all all right! ♪
‎（90年代秀）
‎你好 威斯康辛！
[young woman] Hello, Wisconsin!
‎酷爱小子？
The Kool-Aid Man?
‎这就是你想要的纹身？
That's the tattoo you wanna get?
‎关键是不要想太多
The key is to not overthink it.
‎任务完成
Mission accomplished.
‎杰伊 我好想你
‎你不能来玩儿我好难过
Jay, I miss you, and I feel so bad
you can't be here for all the fun.
‎格温和奥兹在说话
Gwen and Ozzie are talking.
‎妮基在嚼口香糖
Nikki's chewing gum.
‎内特在那里拽裤裆
And Nate's adjusting his junk.
‎亲 你得多抹点爽身粉
You need more powder, babe.
‎一到夏天 裤裆就遭殃
Summer's the worst season for your junk.
‎我能跟他聊几句吗？
Hey. Can I talk to him?
‎哥们儿 你就来吧
Just come over, bro.
‎莉亚的奶奶去看牙医了
‎雷德去车管局了
Leia's grandma's at the dentist.
Red's stuck at the DMV.
‎该死 我也想你
Damn it. I miss you too.
‎-他要过来了
‎-是吗？
-He's coming over.
-He is?
‎我得刮刮腋毛
I gotta shave my pits!
‎什么？
[Jay] Uh, what?
‎是妮基说的 拜拜
[nervous chuckle] That was Nikki. Bye!
‎格温 帮帮我
Gwen. Help me.
‎有男友第一日
Boyfriend, day one.
‎我也得走了
Oh, I gotta take off too.
‎我和高考补习老师约了20分钟后见
I'm meeting my SAT tutor in 20 minutes.
‎又是那家伙？
Again with that guy?
‎但你已经很聪明了
‎你帮我逃出了那个蹦床
But you're already so smart.
You helped me escape from that trampoline.
‎亲爱的 我得拿个好分数
‎考进好大学 攻克疑难病症
Babe, I need to ace the SATs,
get into a good college, cure a disease,
‎把我的脸印在邮票上
‎这样我那些死对头就得拿舌头舔
and have my face on a stamp
so my enemies can lick it.
‎她和补习的家伙
‎相处的时间可不短呢
She's spending a lot of time
with that tutor guy.
‎某人在吃醋吗？
Is someone feeling jealous?
‎没有啊 是我在吃醋
No, I am.
‎她总是跟那个家伙在一起
I mean, she's with this guy all the time.
‎你觉得我需要担心吗？
Do you think I have
anything to worry about?
‎不知道对方是什么人
‎这问题很难回答 但凭我对你的了解
Tough to answer without knowing
who the guy is, but, knowing you,
‎也许吧
maybe.
‎就是说啊 是吧？
I know, right?
‎你要这么介意 那咱们就去打探一下
If it's really bothering you,
let's check this guy out.
‎算了 我应该相信她
Nah, I should just trust her.
‎内特 我看过很多脱口秀 学到了两点
Nate, I watch a lot of talk shows,
and I've learned two things.
‎人会出轨
People cheat.
‎一日破鞋 终身破鞋
And once a ho, always a ho.
[rock music playing]
‎你能来太好了
I'm so happy you're here.
‎不会有事的 往前走三步
It's gonna be okay.
Take three steps forward.
‎不行 万一雷德回来怎么办？
I can't. What if Red comes home?
‎格温 他只是谨慎行事
He is just being smart, Gwen.
‎谨慎 性感 又英勇
Smart and hot and brave.
‎我才不怕谁家爷爷呢
-I'm not scared of somebody's grandpa.
-[coughs]
-[Jay yells]
-[Sherri shrieks]
‎我去！我就是钻空过去而已
Holy hell! I was just
trying to scooch by ya,
‎没想把大伙儿吓成这样
not scare the Milk Duds
out of all of us. [exclaims]
‎嗨 朗克阿姨 抱歉 我奶奶不在家
Hi, Ms. Runck.
Sorry, but my grandma's not home.
‎我知道 我待会去牙医诊所接她
‎因为她的药劲还没过
I know. I gotta pick her up at the dentist
soon because she's gonna be zonked.
‎我想着先过来扫点货
But I thought I'd pop over first
and do a little grocery shoppin'.
‎比大老远跑商店省事多了
So much easier than going
all the way down to the store, ya know?
‎妈妈！
Mom!
‎给我拿点酸奶嘛
-Grab me some yogurts.
-Oh.
‎一看这就是刚刚谈恋爱
Oh, you know it's the beginning
of a relationship
‎放个屁还得躲到门外去
when the guy still goes outside
to cut the cheese.
‎杰伊 你就进来吧
Jay, just come in.
‎-我好想你
‎-我也很想你
-I missed you so much.
-Missed you too.
‎怎么？他刚从伊拉克回来哇？
What? He just get back
from Iraq or something?
‎他们才分开一天而已
‎她爷爷不准他来这里了
They've been apart for one day.
Her grandpa banned him from the house.
‎雷德好像有点像我那个倔老爹
Sounds like Red's being
a hard-ass like my dad.
‎他一点都不相信我
He never believed in me.
‎有时候我怀疑是不是他把我耽误了
Sometimes I wonder
if that might've screwed me up.
‎哎呀呀
No.
‎你真贴心 闺女 但我真这么觉得
Aw, that's nice, hon,
but I really think he did.
‎重点是大人应该更加体谅 知道吗？
The point is, adults should be
more understanding. You know?
‎只知道给娃们立规矩并不是办法
I mean, just throwing rules out at kids
is not the answer.
‎所以你会同意我纹身咯？
So you'll sign off on me getting a tattoo?
‎不好意思 姑娘
Sorry, lady.
‎犯错可以 贻害万年那种可不行
I'm fine with you making mistakes,
but not permanent ones.
‎纹身 怀孕 酒驾 邪恶三位一体
Tattoos, babies, and DUIs,
the unholy trinity.
‎牙科诊所离这里不就五分钟路程吗？
Wait, isn't the dentist
like five minutes away?
‎杰伊 要不咱们去接奶奶吧？
Jay, why don't we go pick up my grandma?
‎我知道这么说不怎么性感
I know this isn't
the sexiest thing I've ever said,
‎但我敢说你爷爷肯定得揍我
but I'm pretty sure
your grandpa can kick my ass.
‎但这样能向他证明你有责任心
But it would show him
how responsible you are.
‎就是 而且你要让雷德明白
Yeah, and while you're at it,
you gotta let Red know
‎你已经受够了他指手画脚
that you're tired of him judging ya.
‎直到今日还让你觉得没用和窝囊
And still, to this day,
making you feel unworthy, disrespected,
‎就好像你不是一个好妈妈
and like you're not a good mom!
‎感觉好像不全是说我们
I feel like that wasn't all about us.
‎我们得试试看
We have to try something.
‎能借一下你的车吗？
Can we borrow your car?
‎我好像不该插手你和你爷爷的事
Don't know if I should get
between you and your grandpa.
‎-我们负责加油
‎-给你钥匙
-We'll fill it up with gas.
-Here's my keys.
‎我就待在这里继续扫货
I'll stay here
and finish up my grocery shopping.
‎我知道你很担心 但我们只是
I know you're worried,
but all we have to do
‎去接我贴心昏沉的奶奶接回家而已
is pick up my sweet, sedated grandma.
♪ Give my regards to Broadway ♪
♪ Remember me to Herald Square ♪
‎轮到你了！
Your turn!
‎那啥那啥那啥那啥 百老汇
♪ Something, something
Something, something, Broadway ♪
‎这首歌老头老太都爱唱！
♪ Old people seem to like this song! ♪
‎精彩收尾！
Big finish!
♪ Give my regards to old Broadway! ♪
‎格温 别再起哄了！
Gwen, stop encouraging her!
‎多好玩啊
But this is fun.
‎她现在嗨到顶天 而且药劲还没过
She's high as a kite that's also on drugs.
[laughs heartily]
‎奶奶 你能不能消停一点？
Grandma, can you please just chill out?
‎切！
Boo!
‎-就是 切！
‎-切！
-Yeah. Yeah. Boo!
-Boo!
‎-等等 我们刚经过纹身店 停车！
‎-算了 格温
-Wait. We just passed a tattoo shop. Stop!
-Forget it, Gwen.
‎我唯一的任务就是把她平安送回家
‎好吧？无论如何 我都不会停车的
My only job is to get her home safe.
Okay? I'm not stopping for anything.
‎红灯！
-Red light!
-[brakes screech]
[exclaims, snorts]
‎拜托
-[Kitty chuckles]
-Come on.
‎我的机会来了
This is my chance.
‎你奶奶现在晕晕乎乎 她会签同意书
Your grandma's out of it.
She'll sign the release.
‎对吧 福尔曼太太？
‎你同意让我纹身 对吧？
Right, Mrs. Forman?
You want me to get a tattoo, don't you?
‎没错 然后我们偷条船 去拉斯维加斯
Yeah. And then let's steal a boat
and go to Vegas.
‎不 我们直接回家 让奶奶上床休息
No. We're going home,
we're putting Grandma to bed,
‎向爷爷证明杰伊是有责任心的人
and we're showing my grandpa
that Jay is a responsible human being.
[rhythmic mouth noises]
‎-猜猜我是谁？
‎-妈呀！
-Guess who?
-Oh my God!
-[laughing]
-[Leia gasps] Oh my God!
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh!
[laughing]
‎我们去去就回
We'll be quick.
‎一会见 呆子们
Later, nerds.
[rock music playing]
‎妮可？
Nik?
‎哟？
[laughing] What?!
‎你？来这儿？
You?! Here?!
‎哦呀呀！
I mean, whoa!
‎现在哇？怎么会？啥？怪事啊
Now? How? What? Weird!
‎我说过我会来这里
I told you I was gonna be here.
‎对哈 跟你的补习老师
Right. Right, with your tutor.
‎我都忘记他了 他人呢？
I totally forgot about him. Where is he?
‎特雷弗啊 他来了
Oh, Trevor? Here he comes.
[seductive funk music playing]
‎我勒个去
[in slow motion] Holy sh-- [bleeped]
[music fades]
‎特雷弗 这是我男朋友 内特
Trevor, this is my boyfriend, Nate.
‎“男朋友”？
"Boyfriend"?
‎“男人”才对 我脸上不太长毛
[snickering] More like "manfriend."
I can't grow any hair on my face,
‎但腰以下茂盛得很
but from the waist down,
it is wall-to-wall carpeting.
‎我是奥兹
[in deep voice] And I'm Ozzie.
‎我的儿科医生说我能长到一米八
My pediatrician said I'll be 6'2".
‎久仰大名
-Oh. I've heard a lot about you.
-[Nate chuckles]
‎她说你是橄榄球队的？
Nikki tells me
you're on the football team?
‎没错 但如果没有
Yeah, but we couldn't do it
‎你们在场下助威 我们也打不好…
without guys like you
in the stands cheering us on. So…
‎特雷弗可是拿到了
‎圣母大学的橄榄球奖学金
Actually, Trevor got
a football scholarship to Notre Dame.
‎其实他也不用指着这个
‎他爸爸是国会议员
Not that he needs it.
His dad's a congressman.
‎天佑美国
God bless America.
‎这么聊好开心
Well, this is fun.
‎也好正常
And normal.
‎谢谢你过来 但我们得继续学习了
Thanks for stopping by, but we really
need to get back to studying.
‎就是 我们今天也很忙
Oh yeah. Super busy day on our end too.
‎奥兹的蜥蜴生病了 我得帮忙喂药
Ozzie's… lizard is sick,
and I have to help with the pills.
‎往屁股里塞那种
They go in the butt.
‎好得很
[chuckles] Okay, cool.
‎幸会 内特 奥兹
Nice to meet you, Nate.
Nice to meet you, Ozzie.
‎我今年25岁
[in normal voice] I'm 25.
[laughs]
‎你完蛋了
You're screwed.
[Leia sighs]
‎怎么这么久？
[both] What's taking so long?
‎我们异口同声 好可爱
Aw, we said that at the same time.
We're adorable.
‎我现在没心思可爱
I can't do adorable right now.
‎如果你爷爷先我们一步到家…
If your grandpa beats us home…
‎-他…会杀了我们的
‎-会杀了我们的
-He's…
-[both] Gonna kill us.
‎好吧 是挺可爱的
Okay, that was cute.
‎总算回来了
Finally.
‎-给我们看看
‎-哦 我没纹
-Let's see it.
-Oh, I bailed on the tattoo.
‎有个女的插队 磨蹭起来没完
Some lady cut in front of me,
and it was taking forever.
‎我纹身了！
I got a tattoo!
‎直奔维加斯！
To Vegas!
[rock music playing]
‎果然是这样
So I was right.
‎那个特雷弗显然想勾引妮基
That Trevor dude is
obviously trying to seduce Nikki.
‎我觉得人家根本不用费劲
I don't think he needs to try very hard.
‎我要怎么拯救自己的恋情？
How am I gonna save my relationship?
‎他又帅又聪明 也不欠妮基70块钱
He's hot. He's smart.
He doesn't owe Nikki 70 bucks.
‎我知道了
I got it.
‎我可以海扁他 可不是嘛！
I'll go kick his ass. Duh!
‎你就是那个“接下来有请”的家伙？
So you're the "let's bring him out" guy.
‎什么人？
The what guy?
‎每个脱口秀都有这么一个人
There's one on every talk show.
‎主持人说：“接下来有请”
The host says, "Let's bring him out."
‎大家都嘘他
Everyone boos.
‎然后他说：“你们又不了解我”
Then he says, "You don't know me."
‎你没看过脱口秀吗？
Have you never seen a talk show?
‎（奥兹秀）
‎奥兹！
-[theme music plays]
-[audience chanting] Ozzie! Ozzie! Ozzie!
‎欢迎回来！
Welcome back!
‎今天我们请到了妮基和特雷弗
Today, we have Nikki and Trevor.
[audience] Aww!
‎他们看起来很像一对神仙眷侣
They may look like the perfect couple,
‎然而 有人对此有意见
but somebody has a problem with that.
‎接下来有请他出场
Let's bring him out.
[theme music plays]
‎切！
[audience] Boo!
‎嘿 你们又不了解我
Hey, you don't know me! You don't know me!
‎内特
Nate.
‎跟我们说说吧 你为什么这么难过？
Why don't you tell us
what's gotten you so upset?
‎这是我女朋友
‎现在她却跟这个家伙在一起
That's my girlfriend,
and now she's hanging out with this chump,
‎突然之间 我就配不上她了
and suddenly I'm not good enough for her.
‎妮基？
Nikki?
‎内特人很好 可是…
‎特雷弗能让我的思想和身体兴奋起来
Nate's fine, but… Trevor stimulates
my mind and my body.
‎同时哇？不可能
-[audience exclaims]
-Both?!
‎同时哇？不可能
That's impossible!
‎对我来说就可能
Not for me.
[audience exclaiming]
‎内特 别闹了
Nate, stop.
‎我不能再糊弄下去了
‎妮可 你必须做出选择
I'm done playing around.
Nik, you need to make a choice.
‎你要他？还是要我？
Is it him? Or is it me?
‎那我要他
Oh, then him.
‎这家伙？
This guy?!
‎你又不了解他
You don't know him.
‎你不了解他
[audience exclaims]
‎-闭嘴 你们又不了解我！
‎-切！
Shut up! You don't know me!
‎-闭嘴 你们又不了解我！
‎-切！
-[audience booing]
-You don't know me!
‎没人认识你
Nobody knows you.
‎别再说了
Stop saying that.
‎（奥兹秀）
-[theme music plays]
-[audience cheering]
‎我得跟妮基谈谈
I need to talk to Nikki.
‎-你要对她说什么？
‎-越聊越诡异了 老兄
-And what are you gonna say to her?
-This is getting weird, dude.
‎我们马上回来
We'll be right back.
[rock music playing]
‎纹身？
A tattoo?!
‎我连防水睫毛膏都不用
I don't even wear waterproof mascara.
‎雷德会杀了我的
Red's gonna kill me.
‎格温
Gwen.
‎我知道
‎但我阻止她在后腰纹铁丝网了
I know. But I stopped her
from getting a barbed wire tramp stamp.
‎所以 不客气
So you're welcome.
‎奶奶 对不起 事情本不该这样的
Grandma, I am so sorry.
None of this was supposed to happen.
‎你怎么做上饭了？
How are you cooking dinner now?
‎一觉醒来 多了一个该死的纹身
‎做饭能帮我缓解压力
It is helping me deal with the stress
of waking up with a flipping tattoo!
‎有什么急事？
What's the emergency?
‎鸡蛋没了？我可不知道咋回事
D'you run out of eggs?
'Cause I don't know how that happened.
‎你瞅瞅 看牙看出什么来了
Look what happened at the dentist.
‎我的亲妈啊！
Holy crapola!
‎听说有的大夫会趁人晕乎毛手毛脚
‎但这也太过分了
I heard of them feeling you up
when you're out, but this crosses a line.
‎我妈会气得敲棺材板了
My mother would be rolling in her grave,
‎只可惜我们把她的骨灰
if we hadn't spread her ashes
‎洒在了她教堂旁边“时时乐”的停车场
in the parking lot
of the Sizzler by her church.
‎你也纹身了？
Did you get one too?
‎你一直吵吵着要纹身
You've been talking nonstop about tatties.
‎不 你告诉我别纹 我可听话了
No. You told me not to get one,
and I always follow what you tell me.
‎很好 一旦纹上
‎这辈子就妥妥成破鞋了
Good. Those things are
a one-way ticket to whore town.
‎抱歉
Sorry.
‎你确定这东西去不掉吗？
Are you sure there is no way
to get this off?
‎有没有什么…特殊乳霜之类的？
Is there a… a special cream or something?
‎真要有的话 我胯骨上也不会
If there was I wouldn't have
Fred Flintstone riding a surfboard
‎骑着摩登原始人了
on my hip bone.
[door shuts]
‎是雷德回来了
‎老天爷 他会怎么想啊？
That's Red.
Good Lord, what is he gonna think?
‎他会气炸的
Oh man, he's gonna be pissed.
‎跳脚咆哮 还不给我零花钱
Stomp around,
probably take away my allowance.
‎不好意思 突然想到我老爸
Sorry. It's a Dad flashback.
‎你得赶紧走
You need to get out of here.
‎不 我不能让你顶罪
No, I'm not leaving you here
to take the blame.
‎好得很 如果有他背锅 我就闪了
Cool. If he has
the blame thing covered, I'm out.
‎等一下
Hang on.
‎把这些拿上 家里没新鲜食品了
Take these. We're low on fresh produce.
‎别让爷爷看到你的手腕
[sighs] Don't let Grandpa see your wrist
‎我们先想想怎样告诉他比较好
until we figure out
the best way to tell him.
‎我有事从不瞒着我丈夫 他通情达理
I do not keep things from my husband.
He is a reasonable man.
‎地狱的紧后面有个小房子
Down in hell,
there's this little room in the wayback
‎里面有小鬼往你嘴里屙火
where the devil craps fire
into your mouth.
‎那就是车管局
That's the DMV.
‎亲爱的 你今天还好吗？
How was your day, dear?
‎就是…还…
Oh, it was just… It was…
‎挺好的
It… It was great.
‎没有什么出格的事
Just, like, nothing crazy happened.
‎他在这里做什么？
And what's he doing here?
Um…
‎他从自家园子给奶奶带了一只鸡
He brought Grandma the chicken.
[chuckles] From his garden.
‎对的
Yes.
‎我在做晚餐
I was making supper.
‎我得掏进去
I… I have to get up inside there.
‎嗯 没错
Oh yeah.
‎这回肯定好吃
This is gonna be yummy.
‎想把鸡从你手上拿下来吗？
Wanna take that chicken off your hand?
‎不想
I do not.
‎我要去拿洗好的衣服了
I'm gonna go get the laundry now.
[rock music playing]
‎我对你们很失望
I am so disappointed in you.
‎你们所有人
All of you.
‎但尤其是你 小凯尔索
But especially you, little Kelso.
‎那天我说错了
I was wrong the other day.
‎踢你屁股都是白费力气
You are a complete waste
of a foot in the ass.
‎你从来没有给过他机会
You never even gave him a chance.
‎一听他的姓氏
‎你就打定主意要讨厌他
You decided based on his last name
that you were going to hate him.
‎这太不公平了
This is so unfair.
‎这样我才能找乐子
And that's what makes it fun for me.
‎莉亚 他说得对
Leia, he's right.
‎先生 是我不好 开车的人是我
It is my fault, sir.
I was the one driving.
‎听我说 出这种事 我也觉得不光彩
Look, I'm not proud of what happened,
‎但我相信 吸取错误的教训
‎也是我们成长的关键
but I do believe the mistakes we make
are what turn us into the men we become.
‎我想成为一个配得上你孙女的男友
And I would like to become a man
worthy of dating your granddaughter.
‎-出去
‎-这就走
-Get out.
-Already gone.
‎还有你 回房间去
And you, go to your room.
[door closes]
‎雷德 你是不是有点太苛刻了？
Red, don't you think
you're being a little harsh?
‎的确 他们犯错了 但又没人受伤
Yeah, they made a mistake,
but nobody got hurt.
‎我妻子多了一个纹身
‎就像蹲了监狱似的
My wife is tatted up
like she's doing time at Rikers.
‎我越看它越顺眼了
I'm starting to like it.
‎感觉自己就像《油脂》里的里索
I feel like Rizzo from Grease.
‎我只是让你接凯蒂回家
All I asked you to do
was to give Kitty a simple ride home.
‎你却把活儿甩给孩子们了
‎结果搞得一团糟
But you pawned it off on the kids
and turned it into a circus.
‎你就是过不明白日子
Like everything in your life.
‎你猜怎么的？
You know what?
‎去你的吧
Screw you.
[scoffs]
‎你就知道吹牛
You're such a blowhard.
‎一直被人吆来喝去
‎说我活得一塌糊涂
You know how many years
I spent getting yelled at,
‎你知不知道我忍了多久？
being told how much I messed up?
‎你可以不尊重我
‎但我终于懂得了尊重我自己
So you don't have to respect me,
because I finally respect myself.
‎我才不要继续站在这里听你咆哮
And I don't have to stand here
while you yell at me anymore.
‎而且你从来没教过我骑脚踏车 谢了
And thanks a lot for never teaching me
how to ride a bike!
‎莫非我长得像她老爸？
Do I look like her father?
[Kitty sighs]
‎我给你带了小点心
I brought you a little treat.
‎-她到底什么毛病？
‎-好了 雷德
-What's with her?
-Oh, Red.
‎莉亚还是半大孩子
Leia is a teenager.
‎一身荷尔蒙 分不清好坏
She's bursting with hormones
and bad decisions.
‎我是说雪莉
I was talking about Sherri.
‎她也是一身荷尔蒙 分不清好坏
Well, she's bursting with hormones
and bad decisions too.
‎我是说…
I mean…
‎她要是真对她爸有意见
‎那就冲他吼去
If she has issues with her father,
let her go and yell at him.
‎嗯
Yeah.
‎别人捅娄子
‎却怪到你头上 那滋味可不好受
It's not great when people blame you
for other people's problems.
[grumbles]
‎什么？
What?
‎杰伊跟他爸不一样
Jay is not his father.
‎他本可以逃跑
‎让莉亚承担所有的责任
He could have run off,
let Leia take all the blame.
‎但你也看到他如何保护她 承担责任
But you saw how he stood up for her
and took responsibility.
‎麦克尔凯尔索可没这骨气
Michael Kelso would never have done that.
‎麦克尔凯尔索把自己粘在咱家冰箱上
Michael Kelso glued himself
to our refrigerator.
‎我觉得你的标准定得有点低
I think you're setting the bar kinda low.
‎听我说 雷德 我也会这样
Well, look, Red. I'm guilty of it too.
‎莉亚说得对
Leia's right.
‎我们确实没给过杰伊机会
We never really did give Jay a chance.
-[Red sighs]
-Oh, oh, oh, oh!
‎我知道这个声音 说明你想通了
I know that sound.
It means you're starting to come around.
‎现在你开明一点了…
While you're a little open-minded…
‎还是不喜欢吗？
Do you hate it?
‎其实…还真有点刺激
Well, actually…
-It's kind of adventurous.
-[Kitty giggles]
[murmurs playfully]
Oh!
‎我知道你想干嘛
I know what you're in the mood for.
‎嗯
Yeah. [chuckles]
‎没错！
Yeah!
‎嘿 宝贝
[Nikki] Hey, babe.
‎你没事吧？
Are you okay?
‎你没捏着我的屁股说：“嘿 女士们”
You didn't squeeze my butt
and say, "Hey, ladies."
‎妮可 我有点慌了
Nik, I'm kind of freaking out about us.
‎-你老跟那个特雷弗在一起…
‎-特雷弗？
-You've been spending time with Trevor--
-Trevor?
‎内特 我和特雷弗之间没什么
Nate, there's nothing
between me and Trevor.
‎你知道我不喜欢肌肉男
You know I don't like muscular guys.
‎这话听得我心情好复杂 不过…
I don't know how I feel about that, but…
‎不只是他 还有很多别的事
It's not just him.
It's all this other stuff.
‎高考 学习
The SATs, the studying.
‎我怕你会丢下我
I'm afraid you're gonna leave me behind.
‎内特 我上大学不是要丢下你
Nate, I'm not going to college
to leave you behind.
‎我…上大学是为了能有好前途
I'm… I'm going to college
so I can have a future.
‎你的前途里有我吗？
Am I in that future?
‎未来还不确定
Well, the future's not set.
‎只有我们能决定自己的命运
There's no fate
but what we make for ourselves.
‎你好性感 还说《终结者2》的台词
You're hot and you quote Terminator 2!
‎我无法想象不跟你在一起会怎样
I can't imagine not being with you.
‎答应我 我们永远会在一起
I need you to tell me
we're always gonna be together.
‎嘿 过来
Hey, come here.
‎宝贝 我不知道以后会怎样
‎我只知道 我爱你
Babe, I don't know what's gonna happen.
All I know is that I love you.
‎我希望这就足够了
And I hope that's enough.
‎是的
It is.
‎-感觉好点了吗？
‎-是啊
-Feeling better?
-Yeah.
‎嘿 女士们
Hello, ladies. [chuckles]
‎好了 我得回家吃晚餐了
Okay, well I have to head home for dinner.
‎-你确定你没事？
‎-是啊
-Are you sure you're okay?
-Yeah.
‎-嗯 没错
‎-好的
-Yeah, totally.
-Okay.
[melancholic rock music playing]
‎（时尚）
[knocking]
‎嘿
Hey there.
‎听着 孩子 我想了想
Listen, kiddo. I've been thinking.
‎如果你真想跟凯尔索家的小子交往
If you really want to see this Kelso kid,
‎我就给他一个机会
I'll give him a chance.
‎真的吗？
Really?
‎但你要小心 不可以开车兜风
But you gotta be careful.
No more joyrides.
‎而且他不可以上楼来 可以吧？
And he's not allowed upstairs. Fair?
‎太可以了 下次见到杰伊
‎我会把这些话都告诉他
So fair. I'll tell Jay everything
the next time I see him.
‎嗯
Uh-huh.
‎这就走
Already gone.
‎-再见 宝贝
[Leia and Jay] Bye, babe!
[both] Aww!
[rock music playing]
‎我跟凯蒂谈过了 不得不说
I talked to Kitty, and I gotta tell ya,
‎我知道你不是我爸
I know you're not my dad.
‎不说别的 你还活着
For one thing, you're alive.
‎而且你也不是混账
And also you're not a jerk.
‎我们是来聊天的 还是…学习的？
Well, uh, are we here to chat or…
or learn?
‎好了…试试之前练的
Now… like we practiced.
‎我的平衡感应该还不错
[Sherri exhales]
My balance is probably pretty good
‎毕竟踩着高跟鞋醉醺醺回家好多次了
from all those times
I walked home drunk in high heels.
‎我会骑了！
Oh, I'm doing it! I'm doing it!
‎好了 现在拐弯
All right, there you go. Now turn around.
‎嘿 我会骑车了
Hey, I'm doing it.
‎做得好
Good job.
‎-现在刹车 赶紧刹车
‎-哇！
-Now, brake. Okay, now brake.
-Oh, whoa! [screams]
[crashing]
‎你这个白痴！
[Red] You idiot!
‎别担心 我没事
[Sherri] Don't worry. I'm okay.
[rock music playing]
‎字幕翻译：Zeo Niu